<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="digital_trading_introduction">
        This topic explores what happens as digits in a single number are swapped in a manner
        that generates different numbers from it. The idea of digital swapping is not focused
        on the value of the number, but on its digital array.

    </string>

    <string name="digital_example_one">
        We will borrow from the rule of factorial, only this time addressing the number of digits
        and not the value of the number."\n\n"
        5! = 5 x 4 x 3 x 2 x 1 = 120"\n"
        So generally, "\n"
        n! = n x (n-1) x (n - 2) x (n-3)..."\n\n"
        However, this time we will be taking a factorial, not of the value of the number, of the
        number of ways its digigts can be arranged. Ultimately, we will take pair by pair differences
        to observe if there is any pattern emerging."\n\n"

        Note:"\n"
        The rule of factorial is  only a way through, but thi topic is about taking differences
        between similar, but, swapped digits."\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="digital_example_two">
        <!--Example will shall continue-->
        Example: 12 and 21"\n"
        As can be seen the two numbers have different values, however they do appear to be slit
        images of one another...."\n"
        Lazy to type again
    </string>
    <string name="digital_example_three">
        <!--Example will shall continue-->
        Example: 31 - 13 = 18"\n"
        41-14 = 27"\n"

        Note that as the difference between the digits is plus or minus a number the outcome of which
        is a multiple of 9 and the absolute-value factor of which is the digital difference...."\n"
        Lazy to type again"\n"
    </string>
    <!--Digital Trading Axioms-->
    <string name="digital_axiom_one">
        The difference between any, digitally forward, and, digitally reverse, entries is a number
        the quotient by nine of which is some number the extreme digits are replicas of each other."\n"
    </string>
    <string name="digital_axiom_two">
        The difference of any digital combination with its own, other, digital permmutation(s) is
        always a number divisible by 9."\n"
    </string>
    <string name="digital_axiom_three">
        The nature of the repeating digit plus the digital absolute-value-difference of the actual
        difference in value, yield the nature of the consecutive repeat value"\n"
    </string>

    <!--Sums of Digital Trading-->
    <string name="sum_digital_hypothesis">
        \"Numbers the digits of which repeat or finitely recur, stem from the same digital nature.\""\n"
        "\n"
        Example: "\n"
        12 + 21 = 33 "\n"
        23 + 32 = 55 "\n"
        123 + 321 = 444 "\n"
    </string>
    <!--Cubic sums in the sums of the cubes-->
    <string name="sum_digital_cubic_sums">
        CUBIC SUMS IN THE SUMS OF CUBES"\n\n"

        1^3 + 1^3 "\n"
        1 + 1"\n"
        2"\n"
        ---------------------------------"\n"
        (1 + 1)^3 "\n"
        (2)^3"\n"
        8"\n\n"

        2^3 + 2^3 "\n"
        8 + 8"\n"
        16"\n"
        ---------------------------------"\n"
        (2 + 2)^3 "\n"
        (4)^3"\n"
        64"\n"
        ---------------------------------"\n\n"

        Thus,"\n" (x + y)/( x<sup>3</sup> + y )<sup>3</sup> = 4"\n\n"

        For each pair above, divide the outcome of the second row by the outcome of the first row."\n"
        That is, divide the result in the cubic sum by that in the sum of cubes:"\n"

        8/2 = 4"\n"
        64/16 = 4"\n"

        As observed that the quotient is always 4 each time the cubic sum is divided by the sum of cubes,
        a learner can thus deduce from emerging pattern the relationship and formmulate a rule as such."\n\n"

        Note: For a single, specific integer - there exist a relationship between the binomianl sum
        of its cubes and the cube of its binomial sum, the quotient of which is always a constant number 4. "\n"

        The general formula , thus, is as follows:"\n"
        x<sup>3</sup> + x<sup>3</sup> = z"\n"
        (x + x)<sup>3</sup> = z"\n"
        (2x)<sup>3</sup> = z"\n"
        8x<sup>3</sup> = z"\n\n"
        8x<sup>3</sup>/z = 4 "\n"

    </string>
    <!--We can make these notes examples too. Since we have covered other types of examples already-->
    <string name="sum_digital_note1">
        There exist a relationship between Binomial sum of the first degrees and the first degree of
        its binomial sum."\n"
        The quotient of which is unity.
    </string>

    <string name="sum_digital_note2">
        There exist a relationship between Binomial sum of the second degrees and the second degree of
        its binomial sum."\n"
        The quotient of which is a constant number 2."\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="cubic_sums_closing_note">
        Note that the rule changes for polynomials of the 1<sup>st</sup>,2<sup>nd</sup>,3<sup>rd</sup>
        ... n<sup>th</sup> degrees, and that remains with the aspiring mathematician to further
        investigate and draw conclusions in form of mathematical formula."\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="sum_digital_exercise4">
        There exist a relationship between Binomial sum of its nth degrees and the nth degree of its
        binomial sum - the quotient of which is n."\n"
        Verify.
    </string>

    <!--The digital sum of Prime numbers-->
    <string name="sum_digital_prime_numbers">
        Let us experiment with a set of Prime within range(1,100)."\n"
        The following set is generated as a result: "\n"
        p = {1,2,3,5,7,11,13,17,19,23...}"\n"
        "\n"
        Summing up the double digit prime numbers of p we get:"\n"
        p = {1,2,3,5,7,1 + 1, 1 + 3, 1 + 7,1 + 9, 2 + 3, ...}"\n"
        = {1,2,3,5,7,2,4,8,10,5,...}"\n"
        = {1,2,3,5,7,2,4,8,1 + 0,5,...}"\n"
        = {1,2,<b>3</b>,5,7,2,4,8,1,5} "\n"
        "\n"
        Notice that except for the 3 that comes naturally with the set of primes, the consolodited
        set bears no <b>3, 6 and 9</b> (multiples of 3)"\n"
        <!--I will need an Excercise for Digitally Permutted sums for Primes-->
        This means that the set of prime numbers within the given range cannot have digitally permuted sums."\n"

    </string>
    <string name="sum_digital_prime_numbers_exercise1">
        What conclusion can you draw? "\n"
        Can you conclude the same for a three digit range(100 - 999) and an up to infinite range? "\n"
        etc...

    </string>

    <string name="sum_digital_prime_commutative">
        Prime Elements of Commutative Digits: "\n"
        31 ~ 31"\n"
        17 ~ 71"\n"
        19 ~ 91"\n"
    </string>
    <string name="sum_digital_prime_non_commut">
        Prime Elements of Non-Commutative Digits: "\n"
        23 ~ 32"\n"
        29 ~ 92"\n"
        41 ~ 14"\n"
    </string>


</resources>