<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="specialDecimal_note">
        Here we will focus on squaring decimal numbers and trying to predict the outcome based on a
        pattern that emerges. Even though it is limitless, since decimal numbers are infinitely
        many, we will however, make it brief thereby living most of it in the hands of the
        experimenter/explorer/investigator."\n\n"
    </string>

    <!--Decimals of the nth Degree-->
    <string name="decimal_square">
        SQUARE DECIMAL"\n"
        If <i>n</i> is a positive integer, then <i>(n + 0.5) or (n + <sup>1</sup>/<sup>2</sup> )</i>
        is any decimal number such that the integer becomes increased by half. "\n"
        Take a number like 1.5, for instance, where 1.5 is a positive integer increased by half. "\n"
        Note that <i>n</i> could just, generally, be an integer - we restrict this study to positive
        integers by choice, otherwise it does not alter the course. If we square the decimal number,
        the following is what we get: "\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="decimal_example1">
        (1.5)<sup>2</sup> = (1.5)(1.5) = 2.25 "\n"
        or"\n"
        1.5"\n"
        x 1.5"\n"
        -------------------------"\n"
        0.75"\n"
        15.0"\n"
        -------------------------"\n"
        = 2.25 "\n\n"
        This is a well-known old method used for multiplication without a calculator."\n"

    </string>

    <string name="decimal_example2">
        (2.5)<sup>2</sup> = (2.5)(2.5) = 6.25 "\n"
        or"\n"
        2.5"\n"
        x 2.5"\n"
        -------------------------"\n"
        125"\n"
        50.0"\n"
        -------------------------"\n"
        = 6.25 "\n\n"
        This is a well-known old method used for multiplication without a calculator."\n"

    </string>

    <string name="decimal_cubic">
        CUBIC DECIMAL"\n"
        This section and the rest, in higher exponents to the nth degree, is left for the user to
        experiment,investigate, explore and hope to formulate a general solution in the end."\n\n"

        On the other hand we should note that the <i>Zeroth Decimal</i> was ignored because it is
        nothing other than unity - since any number raised to zero is one. The first decimal was
        neglected, as well, since any number raised to unity is the number itself. "\n"
    </string>

    <!--Decimal of the Negative nth degree-->
    <string name="negative_decimal">
        This section is left majorly on the shoulders of an investigator, since it is a build-up
        of the previous topic."\n"
        PER SQUARE DECIMAL "\n"
        <i>(1.5)<sup>-2</sup> OR <sup>1</sup>/<sup>(1.5)<sup>2</sup>></sup></i>"\n\n"
        PER CUBE DECIMAL "\n"
        <i>(1.5)<sup>-3</sup> OR <sup>1</sup>/<sup>(1.5)<sup>3</sup>></sup></i>"\n\n"
        PER NTH DECIMAL "\n"
        <i>(1.5)<sup>-n</sup> OR <sup>1</sup>/<sup>(1.5)<sup>n</sup>></sup></i>"\n"
        for <i>n > 0</i> and, conveniently, an element of positive integers.
    </string>

    <!--Abridging Coincidences-->
    <string name="ac_intro">
        <i>(n(n + n) - n)/n = n + (n - 1)</i>"\n"
        The formula is graphic in it's nature to accurate the relationship of all four mathematical
        operative signs(+, - , x, /), even though it translates to consolidated forms below. "\n\n"

        <i>(n(2n) - n)/n = n + (n - 1)</i>"\n"
        <i>(2n<sup>2</sup> - n)/n = (2n - 1)</i>"\n"

    </string>

    <string name="ac_example">
        Example: Let n = 5 "\n"

        <i>(2(5)<sup>2</sup> - 5)/5 = (2(5) - 1)</i>"\n"

        "\n"
        Note that the above equations equip an investigator with factoristion and factorisation by
        grouping skills."\n\n"

    </string>

</resources>